oh, take away the cloth, please,
ой у т тряпочку убери пожалуйста
communication will not cause any damage.
общение не будет никакую повреждений
we can star ball here I have to get
сейчас можем звезду ball вот у меня к
better andrey pop stars kabul how
налаживаться андрей поп-звезд кабул как
like andrey folders milena andrey popok
как андрей папок милена андрей попок
report such a name for you search that you are a
отчет такую за фамилии ты поиску что ты
Pole
поляк
you don’t know Russian
вы русский язык не знаете
but papuk is a butt as the priests
но папук это попка как священников
were called in the Russian empire in the
называли в российской империи в
Russian empire yes and
российской империи да а
now  in a different way, yes, in a different way,
сейчас по-другому да по другому
what was the name of the popes were they, and
как поп назывался папы были ними а
now and now there is a holy father or
сейчас а сейчас там святой отец или
then okay, look so that the conclusion
тогда окей смотрите дабы интерес вывод
by nationality is interesting, who I look at in the USSR from
по национальности кто я смотрю в ссср из
some kind of nationality they
какой то так да по национальности
were saved because you had mom and
спасались так как то у вас мама и папа
dad  by nationality, too, the heart and they
были по национальности тоже сердце и они
were not with Tony were the Chinese Republic
не были с тони были китайской республики
no less than vodka the road from where from
не не менее водку дорога с откуда с
which region as he said more  az
какой области как его сказал еще раз
fold andrey folders
сложи андрей папок
dry ass
dry попка
intellectually difficult 11 letters and this is where
интеллектуально сложно 11 букв а это где
wait in the end or where is that bi bi to bi
подожди в итоге или где ту би би ту би
right about you can now find yes
прям про можно сейчас можно найти да
come on come on
давай давай
andrey ass
андрей попка
like Dator's joke like in first grade
типа шутка датора как в первом классе
no interest your viewers are also folders or
нет интерес ваши зрители тоже папок или
letter by letter  like if you write in Russian then
по буквам как если по-русски писать то
through the letter and daddy it’s in Ukrainian and
через букву и папик это по-украински и
write daddy like this new
напишите папик вот так новый
Russian
русский у
you have a stream right now choosing s3 mini food I
тебя щас стрима выбирая s3 mini еду я
just have conversations in mind there is an interesting
просто беседы виду есть интересная
conversation of water
беседа воды
before your last they stream you here
до вашего последний они стрим тебя вот
it is written after 2103 not this  5 pm my
написано после 2103 не это 5 вечера my
doing and talking to eat in the me in
делаете и беседы to eat in the мне в
living cells and 20 hours ago wrote
живые клетки и 20 часов назад написал
something here show how you
что-то тут показывайте как у вас
have some troops here and
какие-то войска тут а
bayraktar something knocks down something like a
байрактар что-то там сбивает как бы
Russian then at the table of trouble
русский то за столом беды
oh scary scary
ой страшно страшно
very  scary, you specifically
очень страшно вы украину специально
chose ukraine for all the cells, of
выбрали на все клеточки
course, but why is this
конечно конечно а для чего вот какая
your motivation to immediately
ваша мотивация сразу подписаться не
subscribe?  Yes, so who will
людям которые утешали же так кто будет
watch it, but Ukraine
смотреть его смотрят а вот украине цвет
will be the color of the SS man, I will call Klintsy, I
эсэсовец будет я зову клинцы я за ним
will sign for him if you write down the
подпишусь случае если будешь запишу
disputes, show it all shows
спорам покажи вот это все показывает
faded away so that’s how kaklam like this
угасла так вот чем каклам вот так вот
so that the ultrasound sat down and read what is written there
чтобы узи сел прочитали а что там
what you didn’t read  I didn’t have time, I can’t see the
чего не прочитал не успел не не видно
campaign, we’re not doing very crazy work, the
поход делаем не очень ума работы была
camera was just not very clear
камера просто не совсем четко и
and I would raise the T-shirt higher, it wouldn’t hit the
выше поднять футболку бы не попадает в
camera
камеру
[laughter]
[смех]
it's just the other way around below 6
конечно это как раз наоборот ниже по 6
we are now a little bit down the stirrups
мы сейчас еще чуть по стремена же шутки
university level jokes
университетского уровня
[laugh]
[смех]
you are good you tell me you were born in the
вы хорошо ты рассказывай мне ты рожден в
ussr but i think like you are not me 81 you are
ссср но я думаю как и ты не я 81 года ты
what
какого
i am 85
я 85
and
и
really really just have young people there
реально реально просто есть молодежь там
puts on yourself here you are a real neighbor
надевает на себя вот ты реальные соседка
kia tell me what you remember about
kia расскажи чем вот тебе запомнилось
life in the ussr
жизнь в ссср
what does it mean you remember well yamaguchi the
что значит запомнилась ну ямагути
story is not cool hugs I can
рассказ нет чем крут объятиях я могу
only tell you by telling
тебе рассказать только по рассказываем
your parents and grandfather  come on, yes, here’s
своих родителей и дедов давай да вот
grandfather’s tales, come on, that’s what was cool
дедовские сказки давай вот чем круто
,
было
but
ну а
now I won’t tell because it’s
сейчас не буду рассказывать потому что
better to tell me
лучше расскажи
you put on a T-shirt born in the
ты напялил на себя футболку рожден в
USSR and what was in that USSR that you were
ссср а что в том ссср такова была что ты
proud of it
этим гордиться
I
я
people were other common to a friend I’ll tell you
люди были другие общие другу я те скажу
if  you now or you yourself were
если вы сейчас или вы сами были
normal now grown up like
нормального сейчас выросли дебилом как
a [ __ ] what if now the other was
это другие что если сейчас другой был
taller
выше
to be with you if now was the ussr
чтобы с вами была если сейчас был ссср
still with me yes well I’m like in the gulag
до сих пор со мной да ну я типа в гулаге
I don’t know what the sausage
не знаю что колбаса
I just saw it’s a
я просто увидел
pity such ussrs and exploded  Damn, I
жалко такие ссср и взорвался блин я
love their freaks for a century, the Russians were pushing there from the
обожаю их чудики веке там наседали от
USSR,
ссср
you want that
русские вы хотите тот
rebuilding in your own
отстройке у себя в этот
queues then
очередями тогда
who is preventing you from doing this or without the Baltic countries of
кто мешает сделать этот или без стран
Ukraine it seemed like this is assassin's
балтии украины казалось это assassin's
arnie the trinity why is it so the
арни троица она почему так может
problem you
проблема вас
subscribe to the channel put like
подписывайтесь на канал ставьте лайк
subscribe frame across the steppe  moved so who
подписывай рама по степи двигало так кто
still respects the goal of the channel meat to get the
уважает еще цель канал мясо достать
right ailments, maybe Peter's boarding school
право недуги может и петром интернатом
test in the office and on May 3 suit growth
тест в офисе так и 3 мая масть росту
I judge information about the mi channel  my and my
сужу мы информацию про канал мимо и моих
[laughter]
[смех]
glory to ukraine two stages of sidorov
слава украине два этапа сидорова